<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>D8 Services Ltd. HK</title>
    <link href="https://www.d8services.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.d8services.com" />
    <updated>2021-07-23T17:29:14+07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>D8 Services</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.d8services.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Services</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/services/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/services/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T17:29:14+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     D8 Services has a combined experience of over 50 years in technical delivery and working in the outsourced environment.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div><div><img loading="lazy" alt="Services Graphic" src="https://d3bsvdgf60iv2h.cloudfront.net/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_005.jpg?itok=LBWwuNR0" data-is-external-image="true" ></div>
<div>
D8 Services has a combined experience of over 50 years in technical delivery and working in the outsourced environment. Services provided include:
<ul><li><a href="../jamf-msp" title="Managed Solution Provider (MSP)">Managed Solution Provider (MSP)</a></li>
<li>Logistic support of large scale deployments / projects</li>
<li>Roll-out and integration of software products</li>
<li>Contract software support</li>
<li>Training</li>
<li>Project Management</li>
<li>IT systems consultancy</li>
</ul><p>Looking for a managed solution, D8 Services offers a Managed Solution for Apple's iOS, Mac OS X and a BYOD (Bring Your Own Device, which includes Android). To view information on this please feel free to view our <a href="msp">Managed Solution Provider</a> page. Outsourced technical services are the most important arena for corporate and education to get right. Ensuring the accurate and time efficent delivery of services can be both fraught with time wasting and frustration. D8 Services has participated in hundreds of out-sourced projects and can employ their expertise to ensure the smooth and efficient execution of your project.</p></div></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jamf MSP</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/jamf-msp/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/jamf-msp/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T17:18:33+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     If the requirements for your iOS, OSX (Apple Management) or BYOD does not warrant a huge outlay, D8 Services&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div><div><img loading="lazy" alt="Services Graphic" src="https://d8web.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_005.jpg?itok=LBWwuNR0" data-is-external-image="true" ></div>
<div>
If the requirements for your iOS, OSX (Apple Management) or BYOD does not warrant a huge outlay, D8 Services can assist by providing a managed solution for either education, government or corporate. Onsite solution could include:
<ul><li>Installation on an existing in house server</li>
<li>Design and delivery of tailored VM appliance</li>
<li>Design of deployment solution</li>
<li>Implementation of site wide software distribution</li>
<li>Ongoing maintenance</li>
<li>Upgrades provided as needed</li>
<li>Support or management of client systems</li>
<li>Remote management (required)</li>
</ul><p>Remote server solution:</p>
<ul><li>Hosted Server by D8 Services</li>
<li>Automated nightly backup to enterprise backup solution</li>
<li>Design of deployment solution</li>
<li>Implementation of site wide software distribution</li>
<li>Ongoing maintenance</li>
<li>Upgrades provided as needed</li>
<li>Support or management of client systems via remote support or onsite</li>
<li>Ongoing support and management</li>
</ul><p>Solution can provide as complex or simple a solution as required by your organisation. The design can be based on your needs and although the server setup may appear replicated the solution is purely designed for your needs. These customisations can include push services to your devices, event notifications, event changes (utilising your current infrastructure. Custom login text on OSX, iOS App deployment via VPP and recommendations delivered through best practises from vendors. By outsourcing your Apple iOS, Apple Mac OS or BYOD (iOS and Android) managed service to D8 Services, you can rest assured that your server is maintained and kept up to date by a certified JAMF Software Integrator with the latest stable releases. The support provided will be tailored to your site and remote management will be established at the start of the agreement.</p></div></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jamf Training</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/jamf-training/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/jamf-training/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T17:16:54+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     & Jamf offers several training programs for your organsations certification requirements.& & Course Pre-requisite Jamf 100 No Pre-requisite Jamf&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div><div><img loading="lazy" alt="Products Graphic" src="https://d8web.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_003_2.jpg?itok=w7_G0lRy" data-is-external-image="true" ></div>
<div>&</div>
<div>Jamf offers several training programs for your organsations certification requirements.&</div>
<div>&</div>
<div>
<table border="1" cellpadding="5" cellspacing="1">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			 <th bgcolor="000000"><font color="white">Course</font></th>
			<th bgcolor="000000"><font color="white">Pre-requisite
		</font></th></tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Jamf 100</td>
			<td>No Pre-requisite</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Jamf 200</td>
			<td>No Pre-requisite - Jamf 100 suggested (recommended by D8 Services)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Jamf 300</td>
			<td>Jamf 200 Required</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Jamf 400</td>
			<td>Jamf 300 Required</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>

<h3><strong>Jamf 100 Course</strong></h3>

<p>The Jamf 100 Course offers an introduction to Jamf Pro and managing Apple devices. This course covers foundations for macOS, iOS, tvOS and Jamf Pro server. The Jamf 100 Course is self-paced, completely free, and offered online.</p>

<p><strong>Topics</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Introduction to Jamf Pro</li>
	<li>macOS, iOS, and tvOS foundations</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Prerequisites</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>None</li>
</ul>

<h3><strong>Jamf 200 Course</strong></h3>

<p>The Jamf 200 Course (formerly Certified Casper Technician) builds upon the features learned in the Jamf 100 Course and takes a deeper, more hands-on approach to Apple device management with Jamf Pro.</p>

<p><strong>Topics</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Further explanation of Jamf Pro and Apple services</li>
	<li>Deployment, security and configuration techniques</li>
	<li>Building and managing content for deployment</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Prerequisites</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Abundant hands-on experience with macOS and iOS</li>
	<li>Completion of the Jamf 100 Course is strongly recommended</li>
</ul>

<h3><strong>Jamf 300 Course</strong></h3>

<p>The Jamf 300 Course (formerly Certified Casper Admin) builds on the IT professional’s knowledge of Jamf Pro and the macOS/iOS platforms. The course applies a scenario and challenge-based examination for the management of Apple devices.</p>

<p><strong>Topics</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Security management workflows</li>
	<li>Patch Management</li>
	<li>Advanced Packaging</li>
	<li>Shell Scripting</li>
	<li>Jamf Pro API</li>
	<li>Advanced policies</li>
	<li>Self Service Customization/Branding</li>
	<li>Jamf Pro Infrastructure (Sites, Network Segments, Distribution Points)</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Prerequisites</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Jamf Certified Tech or</li>
	<li>Jamf Certified Admin or</li>
	<li>Jamf Certified Expert or</li>
	<li>Certified Casper Technician (CCT) v9 or</li>
	<li>Certified Casper Admin (CCA) v9 or</li>
	<li>Certified Casper Expert (CCE) v9</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Prerequisites:</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Experience manipulating scripts and configuration files in a command line interface</li>
	<li>Windows and Linux familiarity</li>
	<li>Virtual machine setup, use, and manipulation</li>
	<li>Broad Jamf Pro capability and device management understanding</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>What's Included:</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Four days of lab-style, scenario and workflow-based learning, and peer discussion</li>
	<li>All hardware and software required for the course</li>
	<li>Printed course materials</li>
	<li>Jamf Certified Server Admin badge on your Jamf Nation profile (upon successfully completing the exam with a passing score)</li>
</ul>

<h3><strong>Jamf 400 Course</strong></h3>

<p>The Jamf 400 Course (formerly Certified Casper Expert) strengthens and expands the IT professional’s skill set with Jamf Pro and macOS. The course takes a deep dive into macOS management through real-world, challenge-based scenarios.</p>

<p><strong>Topics</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Infrastructure integration for scalable deployments</li>
	<li>Advanced Jamf Pro API usage</li>
	<li>Expert level management workflows</li>
	<li>Advanced Scripting</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Prerequisites</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Jamf Certified Admin or</li>
	<li>Jamf Certified Expert or</li>
	<li>Certified Casper Admin (CCA) v9 or</li>
	<li>Certified Casper Expert (CCE) v9</li>
	<li>Scripting Knowledge</li>
</ul>
</div></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jamf PRO</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/jamf-pro/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/jamf-pro/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T17:15:39+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     As part of D8's service offering we have the most experienced team of Apple and Jamf PRO formerly JAMF&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div><div><img loading="lazy" alt="People Graphic" src="https://d8web.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_003_2.jpg?itok=w7_G0lRy" data-is-external-image="true" ></div>
<div>
<img loading="lazy" alt="Jamf Pro" class="alignnone size-thumbnail wp-image-1597" src="/sites/default/files/Jamf-Pro-color_SM.png" data-is-external-image="true"  title="Jamf PRO"><p>As part of D8's service offering we have the most experienced team of Apple and Jamf PRO formerly JAMF Software's CasperSuite implementation specialists across Asia. Looking for a managed solution, D8 Services offers a Managed Solution for Apple's iOS, Mac OS X and a BYOD (Bring Your Own Device, which includes Android). To view information on this please feel free to read the information below regarding the Casper Suite, or view our <a href="msp">Managed Solution Provider</a> page. We can not only deliver Jamf PRO to your location and fulfil the required initial implementation by Jamf (Jumpstart, see below), but also work with you to provide a superior environment for your users while meeting security requirements of your site. Our services have been used across Asia by educational and corporate institutions alike, including global mangaged solution's. Our service offering can be anywhere from a minimal implementation of the Casper Suite integrating to your existing environment through to a full deployment, customised solutions while also documenting our delivery process for ongoing support by your staff. If however you do not have the in house skills we can be engaged to provide regular maintenance to your solution. While also upgrading software and settings.&With the addition of a VPN connection to your site our support staff can assist on short notice where required. However should you wish to not invest in a local server D8 Services can also provide a hosted solution whereby the server is maintained by us. When the Jamf PRO solution is purchased there is a mandatory requirement of a "Jumpstart". This process delivers an onsite Certified Casper Integrator for 2 days or 2.5 days onsite with you and your IT Support team. Jumpstart Days Explained</p>
<ul><li>2 day JumpStart, Onsite Mac OS management ONLY</li>
<li>3 day JumpStart, Onsite Mac OS 2 days and one day iOS</li>
<li>4+4 remote JumpStart, Remote half day iOS jumpstart performed in one day or across two</li>
</ul><p>Mac OS Jumpstart</p>
<ul><li>Install your Jamf Software Server</li>
<li>Create LDAP connections to existing directory servers</li>
<li>Inventory a subset of your computers</li>
<li>View inventory reports</li>
<li>Create packages</li>
<li>Image computers</li>
<li>Remotely manage computers</li>
<li>Enable Push Services to your Devices</li>
</ul><p>iOS Jumpstart</p>
<ul><li>Enroll devices</li>
<li>Inventory a subset of your iOS Devices</li>
<li>Demonstrate push policies and management</li>
<li>Discuss and advise on a deployment design</li>
</ul><p>Further reading:</p>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jamf.com/services/implementation/">JumpStart Overview</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.jamf.com/products/jamf-pro/">Jamf PRO Overview</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.jamf.com/resources/">JAMF Software: Resources - PDF Library</a></li>
</ul><p>&</p>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contact Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/contact-us/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/contact-us/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T17:08:16+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     D8 Services Limited RM202 2nd&Floor, Lap Fai Building 6-8 Pottinger Street Central, Hong Kong Email: Click Here to send&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <img loading="lazy" alt="Support Graphic" src="https://d8web.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_002_1.jpg?itok=NzUPE49m" data-is-external-image="true" >
  </p>
<div><td>D8 Services Limited<br>
			RM202 2nd&Floor, Lap Fai Building<br>
			6-8 Pottinger Street<br>
			Central, Hong Kong</td></div>
<div><td>Email:</td>
<td><a href="#" onclick="JavaScript:window.location='mailto:'+'info'+'@'+'d8services'+'.com'">Click Here to send an email</a></td>
<a href="#" onclick="JavaScript:window.location='mailto:'+'info'+'@'+'d8services'+'.com'">Click Here to send an email</a>
<td><a href="#" onclick="JavaScript:window.location='mailto:'+'info'+'@'+'d8services'+'.com'">Click Here to send an email</a></td></div>
<div><tr><td>Phone:</td>
<td>+852 66420681</td>
</tr>
<td>Phone:</td>
<td>+852 66420681</td>
<tr><td>Phone:</td>
<td>+852 66420681</td>
</tr></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/about-us/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/about-us/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T14:57:54+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     D8 Services was born to fill a gap in specialised technical Apple services across Asia. In 2010 a group&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div><img loading="lazy" src="https://d8web.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_004.jpg?itok=u7z7BVGY" data-is-external-image="true" ></div>

  <p>
    D8 Services was born to fill a gap in specialised technical Apple services across Asia. In 2010 a group of Australian IT companies and individuals decided to form a Hong Kong based company that would be able to provide the experience and expertise to provide these services. D8 Services specialised IT support has seen work completed throughout Asia and into the Middle East. This work has ranged from training to custom scripting, web site design to onsite IT co-ordinators, Application Design, global software deployment and even email server migrations. D8 Services have delivered end to end solutions, remediated networks and SAN’s which were poorly configured, developed software code and delivered customised web site LDAP management.&nbsp;
  </p>

  <p>
    With an extensive knowledge of video production, our team have also worked under contract for national broadcasters and international television stations. This has seen our experience proven time and time again through education and corporates alike. The staff within D8 Services have the following certifications; Apple Certified Systems Administrator, Apple Certified Technical Co-ordinator XSAN Administrator Bakbone Software NetVault Administrator ,Certified JAMF Jumpstart Integrator, Certified JAMF Tech, Certified JAMF Administrator Certified, Certified JAMF Expert, JAMF Mobile Administrator
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>D8 Services LTD. HK</title>
        <author>
            <name>D8 Services</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.d8services.com/home/"/>
        <id>https://www.d8services.com/home/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-23T17:03:50+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     D8Services have been working across Asia for many years, providing software solutions, project management and consultancy services. Providing a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div><img loading="lazy" src="https://d8web.s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/files/styles/d8_images/public/img_001_0.jpg?itok=PdRuC9qM" data-is-external-image="true" ></div>

  <p>
    D8Services have been working across Asia for many years, providing software solutions, project management and consultancy services. Providing a high level of technical expertise, D8 Services IT experience covers all facets of business and education, with many clients choosing service contracts to continue to protect their infrastructure. We are the preferred service provider for a range of software development firms, with experience in roll-out and integration of software systems across different platforms.<br><br>D8 Services has the ability to deliver Managed Services for your Jamf PRO deployment, with combined experience over 45 years integration and 14 years Jamf Integration work in Hong Kong and across Asia Pacific. We can also assist with the deployment of iOS devices such as iPads and iPhones, with intimate knowledge of the Apple Mac OS and iOS we look forward to working with your organisation.<br><br>Expanding in 2017, D8 Services also achieved trainer status with Jamf, adding the 200 Jamf Tech, 2018 Jamf 300, and in 2021 we achieved the Jamf 400 facilitator to operate within Asia and across Oceana.<br><br><em>&nbsp;- With a highly skilled committed team, there is little that cannot be achieved. -&nbsp;</em>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
